

RAFAEL LARA BERNABE

PROFILE

I am a hard-working, kind person, I enjoy constant learning, which has meant a lot for my academic career at the university where I am currently and I am in the best position to obtain experiences in the aboral field

- +52 232-104-9738
- Constituyentes, S/N, H. Congreso de la Unión, Martinez de la Torre Ver. 93600.
- 162t0432@misantla.tecnm.mx
- linkedin.com/in/rafael-lara-bernabe-6096451a4

TRAINING

June 2020 – June 2020

UDEMY

Master in PHP7, POO, MVC, MySQL, Laravel 6+, Codelgniter 4.

November 2019 – March 2020

PEGA SYSTEM

Certified System Architect

August 2016 – January 2021

Instituto Tecnológico Superior de Misantla

Engineering in Information and Communication Technologies

August 2020 - November

2020

PEGA SYSTEM

Certified Business Architect

EXPERIENCE

March 2020 – January 2021 Professional practices as a developer Inventalab México Integral Engineering Solutions

Data base administrator (MySQL).

Web Developer (PHP, CSS, HTML5, Bootstrap, JavaScript).

Mobile Developer (Flutter).

COMPUTING

Java Script Laravel HTML, CSS

Photoshop

MySQL

PHP

Ms Office

LANGUAGES

Inglés

Español

Servicios Web



RAFAEL LARA BERNABE

PERFIL

Soy una persona trabajadora, amable, disfruto del constante aprendizaje, lo cual ha significado mucho para mi trayectoria académica en la universidad en la que actualmente me encuentro y estoy en la mejor disposición para obtener experiencias en el campo aboral

- +52 232-104-9738
- Constituyentes, S/N, H. Congreso de la Unión, Martinez de la Torre Ver. 93600.
- 162t0432@misantla.tecnm.mx
- linkedin.com/in/rafael-lara-bernabe-6096451a4

FORMACIÓN

Junio 2020 – Junio 2020

UDEMY

Master en PHP7, POO, MVC, MySQL, Laravel 6+, Codelgniter 4.

Noviembre 2019 – Marzo

PEGA SYSTEM

Certified System Architect 2020

2016 - 2021

Instituto Tecnológico Superior de Misantla

Ingeniería en Tecnologías de la Información y Comunicaciones

Agosto 2020 - Noviembre

PEGA SYSTEM 2020

Certified Business Architect

EXPERIENCIA

Marzo 2020 - Enero 2021 Prácticas Profesionales como Desarrollador en Inventalab México Soluciones Integrales de Ingeniería

> Administrador de Base de Datos (MySQL). Desarrollador Web (PHP, CSS, HTML5, Bootstrap, JavaScript). Desarrollador Móvil (Flutter).

INFORMÁTICA

Photoshop Java Script PHP MySQL Ms Office Laravel Servicios Weh HTML, CSS

IDIOMAS

Inglés

Español